http://www.namelab.com/privacy-policy

Names
Approach
LabNotes
Contact
Privacy Policy Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.namelab.com and NameLab, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to NameLab, Inc. include www.namelab.com and NameLab. The NameLab website provides information regarding NameLab’s consulting services. By using the namelab.com, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationWe do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services. These may include: (a) sending us an email message. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.Sharing Information with Third PartiesNameLab does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. NameLab may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail or provide customer support. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to NameLab, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. NameLab may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NameLab or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NameLab; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of NameLab, or the public.Automatically Collected InformationInformation about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by NameLab. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the NameLab website.Use of CookiesThe NameLab website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize NameLab pages, or register with NameLab site or services, a cookie helps NameLab to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same NameLab website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the NameLab features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the NameLab services or websites you visit.LinksThis website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Children Under ThirteenNameLab does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.E-mail CommunicationsFrom time to time, NameLab may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication.Changes to this StatementNameLab reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.Contact InformationNameLab welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that NameLab has not adhered to this Statement, please contact NameLab at:NameLab, Inc.4450 Wolff Street Denver,Colorado 80212Email Address:info@namelab.comTelephone number:415-517-0803Effective as of August 10, 2018
